Preliminary Guide to the John A. Wilson papers, 1974-1993 MS2190
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-1993; Series 3
  - Coop Equality Permanent, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Cooper Houses, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cooperative Association Amendment Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Coops, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 2)
  - Copies of bill - introduced version, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Copies of donation checks, 1982; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Corporation Counsel, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Corrections - Facility Study Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Corrections - Good Time Credit Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Corrections - Inmate Profile, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Corrections - Judiciary, 1987 March 23; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Corrections - Prison State Resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Corrections Downtown facility, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Corruption, 1986-1987; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Cosmetology Regulation, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Council Committee Rules, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Council members - JAW - Downtown Development District, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Council of Goverments, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Councilman John A. Wilson, Foggy Bottom Friends, 1983 April 15; Series 3 (Box 74, Binder 1)
  - Court Decisions, 1986-1989; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - C.O.W., 1992 October 20; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 20)
  - Crime Statistics, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Crime Task Force, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Crosstown Watermain, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Crucifix [found with items from Wilson funeral], Series 3 (Box 83, Item 6)
  - CSF, 1986 April 23; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - CSF, 1986 April 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - CSF, 1986 January 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - CSF Audit, 1981; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CSF Fundraiser, 1987 June 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - CSF Fundraiser, 1986; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - CSF Misc, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CSF Old Info, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CSF Report, 1988 April 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CSF Report, 1988 January 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CSF Report, 1988 July 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - CSF Report, 1988 October 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CSF Report, 1987 October 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - CSF Report, 1987 July 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - CSF Report, 1987 April 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - CSF Report, 1987 January 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - CSF Report, 1986 October 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - CSF Report, 1986 July 01; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - CSF Report, 1985 January 01; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CSF Report, 1984 October 01; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CSF Report, 1985 January 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 3)
  - CSF Report, 1985 April 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 4)
  - CSF Report, 1985 July 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 5)
  - CSF Report, 1985 October 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 8)
  - CSF Report, 1981 June 10; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 9)
  - CSF Report, 1983 October; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 15)
  - CSF Report, 1984 January 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 16)
  - CSF Report, 1984 April 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 17)
  - CSF Report, 1984 July 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 18)
  - CSF Report, 1984 March 03; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 23)
  - CSF Report, 1984 October 10; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 2)
  - CSF Report, 1984 August 10; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 3)
  - CSF Report, 1984 August 10; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 4)
  - CSF Report, 1984 June 10; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 5)
  - CSF Report, 1982 March 10; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 10)
  - CSX railroad, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Cup from the National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 7)
  - Curfew legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Current zoning issues, 1987; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - DC Code research, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - DC Commission for Women, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - DC Convention Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - DC Courts Annual Report, 1982; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - DC Democratic Committee Unity, 1984; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - DC Dept of Corrections, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - DC Election Reform, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - DC Full Service Banking Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - DC General Advisory Board, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - DC General Hospital, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - DC General Hospital oversight, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - DC Habitat for Humanity - NE Parcel 75, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - DC Housing Fin. Agency, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - DC Jail Reduction in Population Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - DC Legal Drinking Age amendment, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - DC Life Underwriters - Norman Hines, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - DC Medical Society, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - DC Parent and Child Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Politics and Power, 1990 November 01; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 26)
  - DC Regional Interstate Banking Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - DC Regional Interstate Banking Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - DC Residency Law, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - DC/Home - AIA, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - DC Statehood Commission -- "New Columbia: 51st State of the Union", undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 15)
  - DCRA Quaterly Reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Death Bills, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Death Penalty, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Death Penalty, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Democratic primary ballot, 1984 September 11; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Democratic Primary Petitions, 1984 September 11; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Democratic Unity Slate, 1992; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Demographics - DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Design Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Development zones, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Diplomatic Reciprocity Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Disabled Parking Residential Visitor Bills, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Domestic Partnership Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Domestic Partnership Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Domestic violence, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Don't Tear it Down, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Downtown Committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Downtown Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Development District - Alternate Housing Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Downtown Partnership, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Downtown Partnership, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Downtown Shaw Neighborhood Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Urban Renewal, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Draft committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 1)
  - Drafts of bill and reports and amendments - Linkage, 1988; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Drinking Age Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Drinking Age to 21, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Mental Illness Insurance Coverage Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Mental Illness Insurance Coverage Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Mental Illness Insurance Coverage Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Drug Eviction Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Drug Eviction legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Drug Free Housing Committee, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Drug Paraphernalia, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Drug problem - 14th St., undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Drug problem - 19th and 0 St NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Drug problem - 5th Riggs St NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Drugs - commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Drugs - Shaw area, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Duke Ellington Bridge Barrier, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Dunnells Duvall and Porter, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - DuPont Circle, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - DuPont Circle Citizens Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - DuPont Circle Group Homes, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - DuPont Circle Group Homes Advisory Council, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - DuPont Circle Political Action, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Dupont Circle profile, 1976 March; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 5a)
    From the donation from Bonnie Wilson, December 7, 2018 (accession 2018.050)
  - DuPont Circle Underground, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - DuPont Circle Zoning Violations, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - DuPont East, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - East End Restudy, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Edes Home Lawsuit, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Education pay raise, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Elayne A. Pollack, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Elise, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Ellington Bridge, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Embassies - 500 foot rule, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Embassy fronts, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Assistance Program Act, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Assistance Program Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Rental Housing Amendment, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Room news story -- WRC TV, 1991 July 26; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 10)
  - Emergency Shelter for Families Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Shelter Services for Families Reform Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Shelters - 27th and I St. NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Emily Perry, 1989; Series 3 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Endorsements, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Endorsements, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Zones, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Ethics Committee of the Counsel - JAW Resolutions, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Evening Exchange, 1990 January 23; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 14)
  - Everett Hall -- Playboy Fashion Show, 1992; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 18)
  - Eye Street Closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Fairlawn Citizens Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Far East Trade Center, 1986; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Far East Trade Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Far East Trade Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Farrakhan Resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Fast Food Restaurants, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Fauntroy's bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Federal City Council, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Federal hate crimes bills, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Federal Health Care information, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Fifth Gould Limited, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Final Mental Health System Implementation Plan, 1986; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Final Mental Helath Implementation Plan, 1986; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Finances - Franchises, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Financial records, 1975-1979; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Financial records, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Finley House, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Fire Department - Annual Report, 1985; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Fire Engine Company #3, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - First presentation, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Flyer, 1980; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - FMS, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - FOAM Container Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Foggy Bottom Airplane noise, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Foggy Bottom bus plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Foggy Bottom Historic District, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Foggy Bottom Historic District, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Foggy Bottom housing properties, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Foggy Bottom News, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Foggy Bottom playground, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Foggy Bottom Shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Ford dealership, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Missions Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Missions and International Agencies, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Forest Haven Consent order, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Fourteenth Street Small Area Study, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Fourways Zoning Case, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Fox TV news interview, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 22)
  - Frances Hughes resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Franchise info - 7-11, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Fraternal Order of Police, 1986; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Fraternity House, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Free Clinic insurance, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Frontier East and West, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Funds Accounting Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Funeral guest books, 1993; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Funeral guest books, 1993; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Funeral guest books, 1993; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Funeral guest books, 1993; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Funeral materials, 1993; Series 3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Some of this materials was added in 2018 and was part of the donation from Bonnie Wilson, December 7, 2018 (accession 2018.050)
  - Gallery House, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Gallery Place Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Gangplank marina tenants, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Garfield Terrace Council, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Gas Station Moratorium, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Gateway Projects, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Gaule Gordon, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gavel, Series 3 (Box 86, Item 3)
  - Gay Pride Resolution, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - General Accounting Office reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - General Public Assistance, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - George Washington University, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - George Washington University, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown ABC Moratorium, 1988; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown Cogeneration Plant BZA case, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Georgetown Floodplain Moratorium Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Georgetown HPRB controversy, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown Incinerator site, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Georgetown Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown police detail, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown Trust Grant Application - opposition, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown University Campus Plan, 1990; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown University Cogeneration Plant, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown University Cogeneration Plant, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown University Cogeneration Plant, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown University Cogeneration Plant, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown Waterfront, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Georgetown waterfront development, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Georgetown waterfront land transfer, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Georgetown Waterfront Park, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Glover Archbold Parkway closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - GPA Assistance Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - GPA Work Transition Hearing, 1987; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Graystone Tennants Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Greater Southeast Community Hospital, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Green Door BZA Case, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Greenline SW/SE, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Greyhound Terminal, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Guest books, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Gun control, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Gun control, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - GW Scholarship Resolutions, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - GWU, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - GWU - West End apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - GWU Bond issue, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - GWU Campus Plan, 1988 April 30; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - GWU Campus Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - GWU Census count, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - GWU Law suit - West End apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - GWU Zoning change, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - H Street NE - PAC, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - H Street NE Business Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - H Street NE minibus, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - H Street NE Parcel Seven, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - H Street NE Post Office Closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - H Street NE, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - H Street Revitalization Program, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - H Street Urban Renewal, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hal Davitt's Fun Fundraiser, 1988 August 18; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Hamilton Arms Apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Hamilton House Apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Handgun manufacturing strict liability, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Harvard, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Head injury legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Health Care, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Health Care, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Health Care Access Protection Act, 1983; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Health Care and Community Residence legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Health Care cost containment, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Health Care resource material, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Health Issues, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Hearing Aid Dealers, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Hearing Aid Dealers and Consumer Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hearing Aid Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Hearing Testimony - Letters, 1987; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hechninger Mall Expansion, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - HED Committee Meeting, 1987 June 17; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Helicopter Landing Pad Prohibition Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - HFA - Home mortgage program, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - HFA Bond Resolutions, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Historic districts, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Historic preservation, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation Review Board, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Historic subdivision, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Homeless, 1989; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Homeless Families Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Homeless shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Homeless shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Homeless women - 619 N Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Homelessness Initiative, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Homesteading, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Homesteading - public roundtable PR 7-115, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Horse Drawn Carriage Prohibition, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Hospice - Gift of Peace, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hotel - Incentive zone, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hotel proposals - New OPD, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Hotels - commercial, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - House of Prayer land - 8th and M, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Housing Finance Agency, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Housing initiatives [1/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Housing initiatives [2/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Housing legislation - ideas, 1987; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Housing Production Commission, 1988; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Housing Production Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Human Services, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Human Services - Annual Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - IBG Development - 23rd and N St. NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Inaugural, 1987; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Increased Penalty for Prostitution Acts, 1985; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Initiative Referendum and Recall, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Initiative 28, 1987; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Insurance - DandA Abuse and Mental Illness Coverage Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Insurance - DandA abuse Mental Illness Health Insurance Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Amendment Act - Prohibition of Discrimination, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Co. Asian/African Development, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Insurance DandA Abuse and Mental Illness Coverage Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Insurance DandA Abuse and Mental Illness Coverage Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Intercity Mortgage Corp., undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Interior Design Amendments, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Interior Design Licensing Correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - International Center, 1983 October 19; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - International Center legislation plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - International Center testimony, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - International Cultural and Trade Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 10)